It will find you.
The Reef: Stalked is a horror, thriller film directed by Andrew Traucki.
After her sister's murder, Nic, her younger sister and two friends
seek solace through a Pacific island kayaking adventure.
Hours into the trip the women are stalked by a shark and must band
together, face their fears and save each other.
Nic, played by Teressa Liane.
Jodie, played by Ann Truong.
Annie, played by Saskia Archer.
Lisa, played by Kate Lister.
Cass, played by Bridget Burt.
Greg, played by Tim Ross.
The Reef: Stalked is a 2022 Australian horror film written and directed by Andrew
Traucki and produced by Jack Christian, Neal Kingston and Michael Robertson.
A spiritual sequel to Traucki's 2010 film The Reef, the film stars Teressa Liane, Ann Truong, Saskia Archer, Kate Lister, and Tim Ross and
follows a group of friends kayaking in tropical waters who soon find themselves fighting for their lives against a great white shark.
The film explores themes of australia, island, shark attack, kayak, sequel.
The tone is dark and intense.